VUONG VO

Albuquerque NM 87102 email@gmail.com 440-000-0000 LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/vovo2
GitHub https://vvo2.github.io
DeepDiveVo https://deepdivevo.com

OBJECTIVE

I am continuously educating myself to innovate better products and software, I want take my creativities and ideas to help a local company grow big.

SKILL

Code with Java, Android, XML, CSS, HTML, SQLite, GitHub, apache server. **Military** communication system and leadership experience. **Education** in art and engineering background, variety of subject and trade skills to incorporate. **Experience** in troubleshooting, technical problem solving, creativity, and innovation.

WORK HISTORY

Private mechanic at John's dealership in Parma, Ohio from 2009 till present. Electrical, mechanic, custom autobody and fabricate new performance parts that's not yet in the market. **Freelance Renovator** in Parma, Ohio from 2012 till present. create new cost effective ways to increase energy efficiency, utilize automated technology thats not yet in the market, innovated whole house electrical and control system. **Technical support** for Asian Town plaza, Cleveland Ohio 2004 till Present. Manage and fixes computer hardwares and softwares, networks, and electrical boards.

MILITARY EXPERIENCE

United States Marine Corps Reserve, Honorable Discharged Corporal, Field Radio Operator Work directly with Officer and Chief to **manage** companies communication sites, **lead** and supervise many retransmission site, technical support for **land and satellite** radio system, **teach** new marines the skills to succeed, **IT** for the entire network of radio system, lead many field **experimental** antena project, deployed and allied with militaries from Europe, Africa, and the Middle East.

EDUCATION

Military Occupational Specialty school, United States Marine Corps, August 2009
Health Information Technology, Cuyahoga Community College, August 2014
Art and Science Associate, Cuyahoga Community College, Ohio December 2016
Deep Dive Java Android SalesForce, Central New Mexico Community College April 2018

VOLUNTARY

Stage technician, light show programmer, Disk Jockey, road trip driver, event planning for Vietnamese church and temple community. **Sound** engineer and studio technician support for various recording and live sound system